English

Privacy Policy
--------------

1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy practices with respect to all Smart Blocker information, data, graphics, content, software applications; the Smart Blocker website, located at [privacy](https://smartblocker.org/privacy) (the “Website”); and other Smart Blocker products or services provided or otherwise made accessible on or through the Software or the Website. Collectively, the Software, the Website, and any other Smart Blocker services are hereinafter referred to as the “Service”. In this Privacy Policy, “we”, “us”, “our” and other similar references mean Smart Blocker and “you” and “your” and other similar references mean any particular user of the Service. This Privacy Policy describes how Smart Blocker uses personal information of users collected through our Service (“Personal Information”).

This policy applies (i) immediately to users who utilize the Service on or after the Effective Date and (ii) on the Effective Date to users who utilize the Service before the Effective Date. Any person who does not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy should not utilize the Service. Each capitalized term not otherwise defined herein shall have the meaning set forth inSection 2.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE EXIT, AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE, THE SERVICE.

2\. Definitions

a) “Contact Information” means (i) your name, (ii) your physical address, (iii) your email address and (iv) your telephone number.  
b) “Effective Date” means the date set forth at the beginning of this document.  
c) “Smart Blocker” means any parent, subsidiary, member, officer, director, employee, or agent of Smart Blocker or any company under common control with Smart Blocker.  
d) “Privacy Policy” means the set of policies set forth in this document.  
g) “User Account” means an account permitting access to the Service, with which is associated a user name and password.  
h) “User Account Information” means information that identifies you to the Service, including your user name, password, internet protocol address, and MAC address.  
i) “User Content” means images, comments, and other materials that you post to the Service.  

3\. Types of Personal Information We Collect

Smart Blocker collects the following types of Personal Information through the Service:

a) Contact Information;  
b) User Account Information;

4\. Mechanisms for Collection of Personal Information

Smart Blocker collects Personal Information (i) upon a user’s creation of a User Account, (ii) upon logging into the Service, (iii) upon interactions with the Service, and (iv) upon uploading User Content to, or generating User Content on, the Service, and (v) when you communicate with Smart Blocker through the Service. When you access our Service, we may place small data files on your computer or other device known as “cookies”. We use cookies to recognize you as a user of the Service. Cookies may remain on your device until you erase them or they expire. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of the Service. You should refer to the help sections of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling cookies.

5\. Purpose of Collection and Use of Personal Information

Smart Blocker uses Personal Information to:

* operate and improve the Service;
* target offers to users;
* administer the Service’s facilities for communications among and between users and the public in general;
* evaluate eligibility of customers for certain offers, products or services;
* evaluate the types of offers, products or services that may be of interest to users;
* provide user support;
* communicate with users regarding support, security, technical issues, commerce, marketing, and transactions;
* facilitate marketing, advertising, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and promotions;
* administer the Service, User Accounts and transactions with respect to User Accounts;
* administer and carry out our obligations under contracts and to comply with the law.

6\. Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our service. Non-personal identification information may include (but not limited to) the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

7\. Storage and Security

We believe the security of your information is a serious issue and we are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We use commercially reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control. Notwithstanding such measures, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Service. We also are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

We may transfer your information to, or maintain it on, computers located outside of your country, in a location having laws that are less protective of your privacy.

We will retain Personal Information only as long as our business needs require. We will then destroy or render unreadable any such information upon disposal.

8\. E-mail Policies

Smart Blocker reserves the right to send you e-mail relating to your account and to the Service. You cannot opt-out of receiving such e-mails, and you agree to receive them.

9\. No Responsibility for Privacy Practices of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. It does not apply to sites that have linked or are redirected to or from the Service (“Third Party Sites”), regardless of whether or not such link or redirection is authorized by Smart Blocker. Third Party Sites may have their own policies regarding privacy, or no policy at all. Smart Blocker is not responsible for Third Party Sites and you use them at your own risk.

10\. Interactions With Others

The Service may contain areas where you may be able to publicly post information, communicate with others such as discussion boards or blogs, review goods, services vendors, and submit media content. Such use is subject to our Terms of Service, and may be viewed by the public at large. Any information, including Personal Information, that you post there will be public, and therefore anyone who accesses such postings will have the ability to read, collect and further disseminate such information.

11\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

Smart Blocker reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Such changes may be announced to you either by email or by the posting of the revised policy on the Service. You are responsible for reviewing both your own email and the Service to determine what is the then-current Privacy Policy.

©2024 Smart Blocker.  All right Reserved  |  [END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT](https://smartblocker.org/terms)  |  [PRIVACY POLICY](https://smartblocker.org/privacy)
